# Ciaran Shaun McLeod

45C Milnbank Road Mobile:07857 513593 • <u>ciaranmcleod02@gmail.com</u>

#### Personal statement

I'm a precise, hard working and energetic person with great team skills and lots of prior experience in acting as a unit whether it being keeping moral up or working on a job together you can count on me to do my part. My goal is to make people happy and comfortable because if everyone spreads positivity then everyone is better off for it. I understand that morale is an important thing to have working in a team and I feel that my light-hearted nature will improve people's moods whenever they're feeling tired, a bit down and ensure the best output from everyone. I'm passionate about the games industry and games technologies as a whole, diving deep into different techniques and personal projects in my spare time.

# **Key Skills**

- Friendly appearance
- · Committed hard worker
- Excited to take on responsibility
- Experience built through personal projects as well as practical education
- Worked with UE5, Unity, Blender, C++, C#, Java, Python, HLSL and Unity's ML Agents

# **Employment History**

#### Piperdam Leisure Resort: Howie's Bar and Grill May 2019 – July 2019

**Duties and Responsibilities:** 

- Making sure the food's presentation is to a high standard
- Dealing with any issues or complaints the customers may bring up
- Making sure the cutlery was polished and ready for customers to use
- Stocking up all the tables with sauces
- Taking orders from customers and putting them through the computers

# Camperdown Zoo Café July 2019 - August 2019

**Duties and Responsibilities:** 

- Serving customers at the till
- Taking and preparing the food orders
- Making various coffees and teas
- Taking food out to tables
- Cleaning tables and making sure the café is clean and presentable

# Search consultancy: Tesco Customer Support Centre July 2021 - September 2021

**Duties and Responsibilities:** 

- Taking calls from customers
- Ensuring the customer feels heard and their concerns are taken seriously
- Solving the customer's issue to the best of my ability
- Logging all details of the call and any actions taken
- Self-reflection for improvement via listening to recordings of my previous calls

### Telefonica UK: O2 Store Sales Advisor July 2022 - June 2024

#### Duties and Responsibilities:

- Handling customer contracts and accounts
- Gaining FCA approval to set up and sell contracts and insurance
- Researching current products, services, and technologies
- Ask customers questions about their lifestyle and what they use their technology for to accurately pitch them the ideal contracts for them
- Meeting sales and review score targets
- Opening and closing the shop
- Ensuring work environment is clean and tidy

# EE & BT: Sales Advisor June 2024 - August 2024

### Duties and Responsibilities:

- Pitch contracts and offers to customers
- Be familiar with company products, services, and technologies
- · Ask customers about their lifestyle and technology usage to effectively pitch to them
- Keep up with sales and review score targets
- Ensuring compliance with the FCA's standards

# Farmstream: Technical Support August 2024 – Ongoing

# Duties and Responsibilities:

- Helping customers with their CCTV and Solar equipment setups and troubleshooting problems
- Diagnosing and repairing CCTV equipment
- Generating and upkeeping API documentation for remote CCTV integration
- Handling company contracts with tech related businesses
- · Packing and shipping customer orders
- Writing documentation and guides for equipment usage
- App QA and polishing

### **Education**

# **Monifeith High School**

(August 2014 – May 2018)

# National 4 levels:

- English
- Mathematics

# **Dundee and Angus college**

(August 2018 – May 2019)

Certificate in Games, Software and Web Design

(August 2019 – April 2020)

**HNC** in Computer Games Programming

(September 2020 – June 2021)

# HND in Computer Games Development

Abertay University (September 2021 – May 2024)

BSc (Hons) Computer Games Applications Development

# References

References are available upon request.